KRYSTSINA BAHDANAVA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



CONTACT

krystsina.bahdanava@gmail.com



in krystsina-bahdanava

LANGUAGES

Polish - B1

English - A2

Russian - C2 (native)

SKILLS

React

React Redux

Redux Saga

JavaScript

TypeScript

HTML5

CSS3

SASS (SCSS)

Git

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

I like computer games. I also enjoy reading fiction, especially fantasy. Listen to music a lot. Occasionally I draw. I interested in Web (UI/UX) design. Beginner Twitch streamer (gaming, of course).

SUMMARY

I am a graduate of the Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics with a degree in Information Technology Software. I have 4+ years of experience in web development, mainly in the frontend. Participated in all stages of the web application development cycle. I have been involved in recruiting and training junior specialists, project management and communication with clients. The main technology stack I use is React, React Redux, Redux Saga, TypeScript. I am able to make requests to various web APIs like REST and GraphQL. In addition, I have experience with Twig (Symfony). Wrote tests using Jest, Storybook documentation. For work I used Ubuntu, Git (Bitbucket and GitLab), Jira (and other Atlassian products), WebStorm (and other JetBrains products). In working with the team, we adhered to the Scrum methodology. I also have experience not only in web development, so I am familiar with other technologies, for example, I can read and write SQL queries.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dec 2016 - Aug 2021

4 yrs 9 mos, Full-time Gdynia, Poland

(Remote work, home office)

Frontend Developer

LoveAMB LTD

- Development and support of web applications using technologies such as React, React Redux, Redux Saga, TypeScript, Web Sockets (Socket.io), Jest, Storybook.
- Support of applications developed in Symfony using the Twig templating engine.
- Participation in all stages of the web application development cycle.
- Recruiting and training junior specialists, project management and communication with clients.
- Remote work with the team using the **Scrum** methodology.

Sep 2015 - Nov 2016

1 yr 3 mos, Full-time Minsk, Belarus Software Engineer

Golden Software of Belarus, Ltd

Development and support of economics and financial applications (Gedemin Platform) using Delphi and Firebird, united a relational database system, post-relational objectoriented technologies of data processing and the language of logical programming Prolog.

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

Minsk, Belarus

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Institute of Information Technologies

Speciality: Information Technology Software

Qualification: Software Engineer

2010 - 2014

Minsk, Belarus

Minsk State Higher Radiotechnical College Speciality: Information Technology Software

Qualification: Technician-programmer